{
    "subject": "resource/Stonewall_Uprising",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Stonewall Uprising",
    "human_readable": "The label of Stonewall Uprising is Stonewall Uprising.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8908306956291199,
            "question": "What event is known as the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8422305583953857,
            "question": "Where did the Stonewall Uprising occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8253072500228882,
            "question": "What was the significance of the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8052625060081482,
            "question": "Who were the main participants in the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7828470468521118,
            "question": "When did the Stonewall Uprising take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7598884105682373,
            "question": "Are there any memorials or landmarks commemorating the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6952725052833557,
            "question": "What were the immediate consequences of the Stonewall Uprising?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369322538375854,
            "question": "How is the legacy of the Stonewall Uprising remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5770111083984375,
            "question": "How did the Stonewall Uprising impact the LGBTQ+ rights movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5672651529312134,
            "question": "What lessons can be learned from the Stonewall Uprising?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Stonewall Uprising is Stonewall Uprising.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3943_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Stonewall Uprising impact the LGBTQ+ rights movement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3943_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the legacy of the Stonewall Uprising remembered today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3943_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the immediate consequences of the Stonewall Uprising?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3943_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3943_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is \"The label of Stonewall Uprising is Stonewall Uprising\".\n\nGiven the context information, here's my evaluation:\n\nThe documents contain multiple descriptions and labels for the event, including:\n- \"The Stonewall Uprising\"\n- \"the Stonewall Riots\"\n- \"the Stonewall Rebellion\"\n- \"Simply Stonewall\"\n\nWhile it is true that some of these labels are used interchangeably, the key point here is whether the label \"Stonewall Uprising\" accurately represents the event. And indeed, all the documents contain this label.\n\nTherefore, I conclude that the triple is correct according to the documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe the events and labels associated with the \"Stonewall Uprising,\" confirming that it is also referred to as the \"Stonewall Uprising.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}